{
    "id": "761e462c4eff4b24974cfd41487fbaa4",
    "title": "Since, For, In, From",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a1000d621a224c79a254cf0ab4340052",
            "title": "Since, For, From, In",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He has been away …………………… six years.",
                    "description": "Use for with perfect tenses to show duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has been learning classical music ………………………… five years.",
                    "description": "Use for with perfect tenses to show duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was here ……………………… two months.",
                    "description": "Use for to show duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t met her ………………………. I left college.",
                    "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are going to Malaysia ……………………….. the summer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have been good friends ……………………….. our school days.",
                    "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long have you been here …………………………?",
                    "description": "Use for to indicate duration. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. when have you been here?",
                    "description": "Use since with perfect tenses to indicate the starting point. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Since",
                        "For",
                        "From"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the best dinner I had …………………….. years.",
                    "description": "Either in or for is possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be here …………………………. 3 o’clock onwards.",
                    "description": "From is used with simple tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The shop is open ……………………….. six in the morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been waiting ………………………. morning.",
                    "description": "Use since to indicate the starting point. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}